The pink is amazing.
Good morning
tea dumplings
hmmm, all of them
One more.
you know, you remind me of that regularly...
Love love love the year
Oh, really?
Love love
It's like a paratiwa.
Wait a minute, plastic.
Wait! It's not in there.
ahahaha shakkola
It's not in there.
Just like on the plate.
It's coming with a charge.
I'm glad you're here.
Good morning.
Now we're going to show you what we've got for you.
Ladies and gentlemen, today we go to Kyoto.
Oh, I made it in time.
Yes!
We've come to Kyoto.
Oh no! I haven't been smooth since yesterday. Since last night.
I came to Kyoto.
What is Junior taking now?
Dumplings!
I thought he was taking pictures of something with great concentration.
It looks like he got dumplings.
I would like to eat them because there is some kind of fruit daifuku with 6 hours of seasoning.
Oh, wow. What is this?
Chestnuts!
Chestnuts are so important.
There were about three of them.
Oh, wow!
This is sticky.
Is it a dumpling?
What are they for?
I got one.
What is it?
It looks like a pear.
Yay! I'm going to eat it then.
I'll go around.
Green tea cream and chestnuts.
Like Daifuku fruit.
Chestnut version, apparently.
And hojicha chocolate.
Get it!
Chocolate.
Hojicha and matcha.
Oh no.
I can't believe I can get this at Mike's Spinos.
It's so cute.
It's cute.
I have to put some distance between us.
I'm gonna have to point out what happened at the show yesterday.
I'm going to get it. I'll stop before.
I was just meeting with my dance teacher.
Pio's.
I have an impact.
That was a cute mistake.
If you work hard today and succeed.
It is absolutely no mistake today.
No mistakes today.
Kids who enjoy themselves are more important than no mistakes.
Enjoy and have fun.
I will do my best.
Please turn your head.
Don't use that earlier.
You know, my house has a lot of peas in a pod.
Surprisingly, spoilers.
Peas.
The peas are cut now.
It was cut.
Ha-ha-ha.
Yes, so, um...
First thing in the morning, I asked Piyo-chan
I asked Piyo-chan to buy me a souvenir
It's called Okoicha Hondan Chocolat.
I don't know...
There's a matcha green tea chocolat that's very strong.
She bought it for me.
I straightened my hair today.
I usually curl my hair, but I don't usually wear it straight.
I decided to straighten it.
How do you like it? Do I look like a sister?
I think I wanted to get some of this.
I got a lot of them.
Matcha green tea.
Here's the star's haircut.
Fic!
So sweet!
Tek-tek-tek-tek-tek.
Oh, it's out of focus.
Oh, he's so cute.
Ha-ha-ha-ha, wait.
Wait, I took it off.
Ha-ha-ha-ha.
Oh, no.Oh, no.
Oh, my God, it's off.
Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Hey, Pio, you can't do that!
Careful, everyone!
It's coming off.
I'll just put them on.
I'll put them on.
Oh, my God.
That's all I want.
I hope that comes through.
Oh, my God, there's no color at all on my lips.
I want to do this haircut with you someday.
Like a view in front of me
I'm sure something will
I want to be
Sushi-in and Hiorin
Oh, I see them.
So cute!
I did it!
I was going to get one, but...
I got two!
I finished two.
Now I'm taking it back to the cashier.
I've been working on it.
You need to lift your foot.
You need a leg up.
Let's go!
Start!
Laughter.
Put out a foot of interest
I can't see.
I'm going!
Let's go!
Laughing.
I'm early!
Please.
Come on.
LOL!
Strawberry guy out!
Pabry Neo!
Shrimp Yorkie.
Error!
Good night.
What's that? Is he here? What a surprise! I'm so happy! You look great!
I'm hungry.
I'm starving.
Thank you very much.
I'll have some.
I was taken a lot of pictures of the kids at Keating's,
Like the V series,
Oh, my God.
You look so natural.
It's like the staff is telling me to get a little fatter.
I can't believe they put all this stuff in there.
What if we can't get into the costumes?
I'm going down to the audience.
I'm hungry.
Knock-on free time goes through here.
That's right. That's where I go.
One shoulder with a flower.
I think the seats here are pretty good.
It looks like it's easy to see everywhere.
It's nice.
How do you like the seats?
I don't feel sleepy.
It's pretty comfortable.
I don't want to put everyone to sleep.
We need to liven it up.
Isn't it nice? This seat here.
It's nice.
I think I like it.
Oh! Nice! It's nice!
Oh, it's nice. You've done a lot of work on this, sister.
It's very easy to see. And the head, you can't see it? It doesn't interfere with the stage? It doesn't cover the stage.
Great, great, if we open this up.
A few millimeters open? A few millimeters. Like, you can't see his face, but a few millimeters, really.
He's out.
They're not here?
Not many.
There's only about four of them.
Over there?
Over there.
Thirty seconds!
One minute elapsed!
Two minutes elapsed!
30 seconds!
Ha-ha-ha-ha!
I didn't see you, did I? I thought I saw your eyes.
You definitely can't see them, can you?
Your hair is weird.
You can't see it, can you?
Oh, don't worry, you can't see it.
Thirty minutes!
Illumination in one minute!
Two minutes!
I saw something.
Oh, you did?
So close!It's close!
On the race!
Aah!
Glowing skin.
Thank you for watching!
Yeah!
All the best.
Sparkle, sparkle, sparkle, sparkle.
Double character.
Sambar.
Ow!
Hahahahaha!
Sambar!
Yeah!
For example, when I say that I
I know Tiorin and Julia,
I know Tiorin and Julia, but I don't want to paint Nui on both of them,
I don't use it that much.
Like this,
Julia's waist might not fit.
Julia is a little bit crazy,
Is she crazy?
I think I'm a little out of it.
Did I eat too much macha?
Maybe. Let me put them on all the way up.
Put them on like this.
Green, purple.
Like this.
It's kind of tacky.
It's fun.
Please try it, too, like this.
Fun.
Shall we prepare the slope? It's not good.
Bye-bye!
You've got mic dust on you.
Hiera bangs.
I used a different spray today!
Mike's bangs!
Look at that.
There's no lies and only the truth My own personal truth
Did you find it?
I found it!
Somewhere east of the world
All I need is a little lipstick and I'm good to go.
It looks really skewed.
I'm not wearing lipstick, so I don't have any color.
I'm so hot!
My hair looks a little like Julia's today.
But it's still done.
See you later.
Thank you for watching.
Come quickly, think of me as Kagenari.
Please do.
I'll do my best.
I won't change. I only want real love.
I found you that day.
Number 3.
Hiyori forgot her earpiece and put it on.
Where's the earpiece?
Where's Aki-chan?
Where is it?
There's no cord.
It's warm!
Julia is practicing her calling.
I wonder how she says it.
Is that an earpiece on?
Yes.
Yes, I'm wearing them.
It's growing back.
Oh my God, I'm in a hurry.
Today is the day of the super-teki-mekki publicity department.
Heart Locked On!
I apologize for the inconvenience.
Heart Rock On Hall Tour 2023
Cute, cute, cute, cute!
Thank you very much for coming to
Thank you very much!
Cute
Announcer mode
Before the meeting, we would like to remind you of a few things
We do not permit photography, recording, or videotaping of any kind, even during the free recording time.
Ladies and gentlemen, the fun is about to begin!
Just a few more minutes, please.
Thank you very much for your time.
It's just like Julia.
I'm hurting myself.
Thank you! Julia!
Maruko! Maruko! Aki! Hiyori!
Super-Tokiimeki Advertising Department
Recording!
I said Poki-Poki-Poki-Poki-Poki-Poki-Poki-Poki-Said
See you next week
Thanks for your time.
I feel like a few of us are going to take the lead and say encore,
I think we all say encore after that.
Voila!
Here we go.Starts.
Recording Free Time.
Hanamichi.
I will see you all when I leave here.
I'm looking forward to it.
I'm off. Bye bye!
Bye bye!
Thank you for your hard work.
Thank you very much.
You did a great job today.
Fabri came too.
Thank you.
I'm being honest, you know, my hair changes.
So it might be different at the next show or something,
You guys can look forward to that too.
It was fun.
Hiroshima.
It was so much fun.
I was so happy to see so many people.
Thank you very much.
Please come again.
I will do my best to preview for everyone again.
Bye bye!
Subscribe to my channel!
I don't know why, but when I laugh, sure enough
It's like the world is shining
I can turn my umbrella around and take it easy
Otherwise I wouldn't be able to walk
I'm sure that somewhere someone is crying
And somewhere I'll get my body wet again
I hope it's not too cold
I'm sure that somewhere someone is crying
Just a little bit of my feelings
I want to share it with you
I don't know what's in front of me again
Come on, let's go wherever you want
Goodbye goodbye, thank you for yesterday
After the rain, the cityscape turns color
And on the canvas of my broken heart, I'll paint shards of the future
Blotting me out
I can say it now
Whenever you're lost, remember the reason for your tears
And when it's raining, I'll smile
Come on, let's go wherever you want
Goodbye Good bye Yesterday's me
After the rain, the streets are shimmering
My heart is fine as I've grown accustomed to it, rainbow pools, make a sound
I play the rainbow piano
Goodbye, Good bye, I was there yesterday
After the rain, the streets are shimmering
My accustomed heart is sunny, rolling tearful clouds
I'll wear a rainbow dress